dreamhosters.com 2006-06-15

# [ DreamHost : Privacy Policy ]

|  When you sign up for service with DreamHost Web Hosting, we collect personal information from you including your name, e-mail address, billing address, security question (and answer), credit card or other payment information, and a password.

We may also collect the URL from which you linked into our site, your IP address, and your browser type and version, all of which are collected in an anonymous manner without being linked to any of your personal information. 

Customer privacy is something we take very seriously at DreamHost. We do not, and have never, sold or disseminated (except in cases where required to by law by law enforcement agencies) the personal information of our customers to any parties outside of DreamHost Web Hosting, or its parent company, New Dream Network, LLC. We use customer information for the purposes of creating and maintaining individual customer accounts, contacting customers in case of a problem with their account, sending personal information, for statistical purposes, to administer our systems, to conduct surveys, to administer drawings or contests, and to provide technical support. All of our development is done in-house, and hence no contracted parties will ever have access to individual customer information. 

Please note that the contact information that you provide to us is used to register your domain name and is, by the very nature of the domain registration system, available for public viewing in many places on the Internet via the use of the 'whois' tool.
